<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Crazy Taxi (USA).gdi</path>
    <name>Crazy Taxi</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Crazy Taxi is an arcade-like racer where the player takes the role of a taxi driver who weaves his way through crowded streets, across sidewalks and even under water, in a wild and frantic race to deliver passengers on time. The courses are largely set inside cities crowded with general traffic and pedestrians (which can&apos;t be run over, they dive away). The main goal is to bring as many customers as possible to their destination in time. Available customers are marked through circles and the colour represents the distance and the fare they offer. Green means long rides with plenty of money, and red ones are very short.</desc>
    <releasedate>20000124T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hitmaker</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Racing</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Crazy Taxi 2 (USA).gdi</path>
    <name>Crazy Taxi 2</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Much like the original, the core gameplay in Crazy Taxi 2 centers around picking people up at destinations which are highlighted with colored rings, and dropping them off at stated destinations.

Crazy Taxi 2 added multiple pickups, which enabled the player to carry multiple passengers, (previously it was restricted to one passenger per journey). The game also saw the introduction of the &quot;Crazy Hop&quot; feature, which allows the player to jump over certain surfaces to save time, as they taxi passengers around the locations. By performing moves such as the &quot;Crazy Hop&quot; and the &quot;Crazy Dash&quot;, the driver accumulates tips from their passengers, which increases the total score.

This sequel includes a modified soundtrack with rock bands The Offspring and Methods of Mayhem. The game also has some online modes in the form of a scoreboard, and replay-sharing.</desc>
    <releasedate>20010529T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hitmaker</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Racing</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Fatal Fury - Mark of the Wolves (USA).gdi</path>
    <name>Fatal Fury - Mark of the Wolves</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>It&apos;s been several years since Geese Howard was defeated in a battle with Terry Bogard, a young man looking to avenge his father. Rather than looking to be saved from death after falling off his office balcony, Geese instead decided to die, and left behind his young son, Rock. Terry took Rock in and became like a big brother to him, raising the boy throughout his life.

Now Rock is a teenager, and Terry is a man in his 30s, and both are about to come together in a new clash...new faces and old come together for the greatest battle yet!</desc>
    <releasedate>20011123T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SNK</developer>
    <publisher>SNK</publisher>
    <genre>Fighting</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Grandia II [Single Disc](US)[DCRES].cdi</path>
    <name>Grandia II</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The story focuses on Ryudo the Geohound (a kind of mercenary) and his talking bird, Skye. Together they accept a mission from the town of Carbo&apos;s church as bodyguards for Elena, a Songstress of Granas, who is on her way to Garmia Tower. The job turns into something much more after an incident at the tower, and Ryudo and Elena find themselves travelling all over the world, meeting some new friends and some new enemies.</desc>
    <releasedate>20001206T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Game Arts</developer>
    <publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Headhunter [PAL][Disc 1].cdi</path>
    <name>Headhunter</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Welcome to the future. In the early 21st century, gang warfare and crime have lead to the creation of privatised law enforcement. The Anti-Crime Network (ACN) employs bounty hunters known as ‘Headhunters’ to track down the most wanted criminals, using combat skills and high-tech weaponry. You are Jack Wade, an ex-cop turned Headhunter. At the beginning of the game you find yourself strapped to an operating table and manage to escape. After passing out in an alley, you awake in hospital from a coma. With your license revoked and few memories, you are hired by Angela Stern, to find her fathers murderer. Maybe you’ll even find out what happened to yourself if you can stay alive long enough… Headhunter is an action adventure viewed from over the shoulder. In the top right of the screen you have a radar which will track your movements and those of the enemy. Jack has a few moves at his disposal. He can duck and roll, push, pull and climb objects as well as flatten himself up against a wall. Using this technique he can peek around corners for a better view of the action, and then attack from this position, using the wall as protection. Between levels, Jack has a motorcycle that he uses to transport himself between various locations in the city according to the clues he receives. You will need to earn skill points however before you can arrive at a destination. Certain parts of the city are unavailable until you have gained the appropriate Headhunter license. As you have no recollection of your past, you have to take a series of licenses that will grant you access to greater parts of the city, weaponry and gadgets. These are taken in a VR simulator known as the Law Enforcement Intelligence and Licence Approval (LEILA). At various times in the game you will need to go to the LEILA building and upgrade your licence by practising your combat, stealth and driving skills.</desc>
    <releasedate>20011116T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Amuze</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Headhunter [PAL][Disc 2].cdi</path>
    <name>Headhunter</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Welcome to the future. In the early 21st century, gang warfare and crime have lead to the creation of privatised law enforcement. The Anti-Crime Network (ACN) employs bounty hunters known as ‘Headhunters’ to track down the most wanted criminals, using combat skills and high-tech weaponry. You are Jack Wade, an ex-cop turned Headhunter. At the beginning of the game you find yourself strapped to an operating table and manage to escape. After passing out in an alley, you awake in hospital from a coma. With your license revoked and few memories, you are hired by Angela Stern, to find her fathers murderer. Maybe you’ll even find out what happened to yourself if you can stay alive long enough… Headhunter is an action adventure viewed from over the shoulder. In the top right of the screen you have a radar which will track your movements and those of the enemy. Jack has a few moves at his disposal. He can duck and roll, push, pull and climb objects as well as flatten himself up against a wall. Using this technique he can peek around corners for a better view of the action, and then attack from this position, using the wall as protection. Between levels, Jack has a motorcycle that he uses to transport himself between various locations in the city according to the clues he receives. You will need to earn skill points however before you can arrive at a destination. Certain parts of the city are unavailable until you have gained the appropriate Headhunter license. As you have no recollection of your past, you have to take a series of licenses that will grant you access to greater parts of the city, weaponry and gadgets. These are taken in a VR simulator known as the Law Enforcement Intelligence and Licence Approval (LEILA). At various times in the game you will need to go to the LEILA building and upgrade your licence by practising your combat, stealth and driving skills.</desc>
    <releasedate>20011116T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Amuze</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Jet Set Radio (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).gdi</path>
    <name>Jet Set Radio</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Tokyo-to, a city not unlike Tokyo, somewhere in Asia, in the near future. This is the story about the GG&apos;s, one of three rival teenage gangs who ride motorised inline skates and are tagging the streets with graffiti. There is a turf war going on between the gangs GG&apos;s, the Poison Jam, and the high-tech freaks, the Noise Tanks. The evil Rokkaku Corporation has the corrupt police in their grasp, and, headed by Captain Onishima, the cops are hell-bent on subduing the unruly teen protagonists. But there is light in the darkness: the underground DJ, &quot;Professor K,&quot; and his Jet Set Radio station keep tabs on what is happening on the streets of Tokyo-to, and soon our teens will have something much darker than the police to worry about.</desc>
    <releasedate>20001101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Smilebit</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/King of Fighters, The - Evolution (USA) (En,Ja,Es,Pt).gdi</path>
    <name>The King of Fighters - Evolution</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate />
    <developer />
    <publisher />
    <genre />
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver (USA).gdi</path>
    <name>Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Soul Reaver is a third-person perspective action game with puzzle-solving and some platforming elements. The game follows Raziel on his quest to purge the land of vampires and take revenge on Kain and his brothers, leaders of the six clans. The player views the environments from behind Raziel&apos;s shoulder, moving him in any direction, climbing, attacking, jumping and using specific abilities. Raziel&apos;s can grip onto the edge of ledges and his torn wings allow him to glide gently downwards. He can also shift through the &quot;material&quot; world into the &quot;spectral&quot; realm at will, but must find specific locations in order to shift back. The two realms mirror one another, with distortions which give access to new areas and platforms. Existing in the material world drains Raziel&apos;s life energy at a constant rate.</desc>
    <releasedate>20000117T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Crystal Dynamics, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Marvel vs. Capcom - Clash of Super Heroes (USA).gdi</path>
    <name>Marvel vs. Capcom - Clash of Super Heroes</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The game takes place within the Marvel comic continuity, as Professor Charles Xavier calls out for heroes to stop him before he merges with the consciousness of Magneto and becomes the being known as Onslaught, the final boss.  While the gameplay was typical of the Marvel vs. Capcom series, Marvel vs. Capcom was distinguishable by two features: the ability to summon assist characters, and the Duo Team Attack.</desc>
    <releasedate>19990325T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Marvel vs. Capcom 2 - House Remix (Hack).cdi</path>
    <name>Marvel vs. Capcom 2 - House Remix</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate />
    <developer />
    <publisher />
    <genre />
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/MSR - Metropolis Street Racer (USA) (Rev. A).gdi</path>
    <name>MSR - Metropolis Street Racer</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate />
    <developer />
    <publisher />
    <genre />
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Resident Evil Code Veronica CD 1 Español (Dreamcast).cdi</path>
    <name>Resident Evil Code Veronica CD 1 Español</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate />
    <developer />
    <publisher />
    <genre />
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Resident Evil Code Veronica CD 2 Español (Dreamcast).cdi</path>
    <name>Resident Evil Code Veronica CD 2 Español</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate />
    <developer />
    <publisher />
    <genre />
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Rez (PAL)[RDC].cdi</path>
    <name>Rez</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>If you like a little style and originality in your first-person shooters, look no further than REZ. Taking the genre to its most viscerally extremes, the game gets most of its luster from its incredible storyline: The information age comes to a deadly halt when the core of society&apos;s technological memory an AI unit called Eden begins to feel the strain of too much data. Struggling to keep up, the technology actually begins to question its own existence and goes into a futuristic freak out. Now, you must journey deep into the realm of 3D cyberspace in order to fix the system, a task that will require hacking codes and battling fierce creatures. Your goal is to get all the way to the system&apos;s core, but that&apos;s a journey that only the bravest and most dedicated adventurers will be able to survive. The game features an incredible array of music samples (you can actually create your own sounds and rhythms to accompany to you on your trip), a plethora of stages, and a list of modes that includes: Score Attack, Beyond, Boss Rush, and Trance Mission. In addition, there are more than 20 hidden features that can be unlocked.</desc>
    <releasedate>20020108T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>United Game Artists</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter, Music</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Shenmue (Europe)(Disc 3 of 4)[DCCM].cdi</path>
    <name>Shenmue</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Includes Original Soundtrack Music Inspired by Yu Suzuki</desc>
    <releasedate>20001106T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega AM2 R&amp;D Division</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Fighting</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Shenmue (Europe)(Disc 2 of 4)[DCCM].cdi</path>
    <name>Shenmue</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Includes Original Soundtrack Music Inspired by Yu Suzuki</desc>
    <releasedate>20001106T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega AM2 R&amp;D Division</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Fighting</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Shenmue (Europe)(Disc 4 of 4)[Passport][DCCM].cdi</path>
    <name>Shenmue</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Includes Original Soundtrack Music Inspired by Yu Suzuki</desc>
    <releasedate>20001106T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega AM2 R&amp;D Division</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Fighting</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Shenmue (USA) (Disc 2).gdi</path>
    <name>Shenmue</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Includes Original Soundtrack Music Inspired by Yu Suzuki</desc>
    <releasedate>20001106T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega AM2 R&amp;D Division</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Fighting</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Shenmue (Europe)(Disc 1 of 4)[DCCM].cdi</path>
    <name>Shenmue</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Includes Original Soundtrack Music Inspired by Yu Suzuki</desc>
    <releasedate>20001106T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega AM2 R&amp;D Division</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Fighting</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Sonic Adventure 2 (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es).gdi</path>
    <name>Sonic Adventure 2</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>After discovering the existence of a secret weapon mentioned in the diary of his grandfather, Gerald Robotnik, Dr. Eggman infiltrates a high-security G.U.N. facility in search of it. This &quot;weapon&quot;, a black hedgehog named Shadow who claims that he is the &quot;Ultimate Life Form&quot;, offers to help Eggman take over the world, telling him to rendezvous with him at the abandoned Space Colony ARK with more Chaos Emeralds. Shadow proceeds in stealing one of the emeralds, and G.U.N. officials mistake him for Sonic. Sonic is apprehended shortly after he confronts Shadow, who demonstrates to Sonic the Chaos Control technique.</desc>
    <releasedate>20010619T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sonic Team</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Soul Calibur (USA)[DCCM].cdi</path>
    <name>Soul Calibur</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>気高き魂を己が剣に宿せ！</desc>
    <releasedate>19990805T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Namco</developer>
    <publisher>Namco</publisher>
    <genre>Fighting</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Star Wars - Episode I - Racer (USA).gdi</path>
    <name>Star Wars - Episode I - Racer</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Star Wars Episode I: Racer is a racing video game based on the podracing sequence featured in Star Wars: Episode I – The Phantom Menace. The game features all of the racers and race course on Tatooine featured in The Phantom Menace. It also adds several new courses, some on Tatooine, others on various planets. Several single player modes, including a tournament mode, are available for play. It also features multiplayer, the format of which varies by platform. Jake Lloyd and Lewis MacLeod, who portrayed Anakin Skywalker and Sebulba in The Phantom Menace, reprise their roles in the game. </desc>
    <releasedate>20000404T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</developer>
    <publisher>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</publisher>
    <genre>Racing</genre>
    <players>4</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Street Fighter III - 3rd Strike - Fight for the Future (Japan).gdi</path>
    <name>Street Fighter III - 3rd Strike - Fight for the Future</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate />
    <developer />
    <publisher />
    <genre />
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Street Fighter III - Double Impact (USA).gdi</path>
    <name>Street Fighter III - Double Impact</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Street Fighter III: Double Impact, known as Street Fighter III: W Impact (ストリートファイターIII Wインパクト) in Japan, is a versus fighting game developed by Capcom exclusively for the Sega Dreamcast. It is a compilation of two arcade fighters - Street Fighter III: New Generation and its update, Street Fighter III 2nd Impact: Giant Attack. As the name suggests, Street Fighter III is a sequel to Street Fighter II. The game was not released in North America.

The Dreamcast would receive Street Fighter III: 3rd Strike, the second update to Street Fighter III.</desc>
    <releasedate>19991216T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Virgin Interactive Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Fighting</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/dreamcast/Virtua Tennis 2 - Sega Professional Tennis (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).gdi</path>
    <name>Virtua Tennis 2 - Sega Professional Tennis</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate />
    <developer />
    <publisher />
    <genre />
    <players />
    <lastplayed>20211211T201946</lastplayed>
    <playcount>1</playcount>
  </game>
</gameList>