<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/3rd Birthday, The (Europe).iso</path>
    <name>The 3rd Birthday</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate />
    <developer />
    <publisher />
    <genre />
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Brothers in Arms - D-Day (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (v1.01).iso</path>
    <name>Brothers in Arms - D-Day</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Experience the intensity of WWII through the stories of Sergeants Baker and Hartsock and your squad of paratroopers during the Normandy invasion. Brothers In Arms D-Day brings players the best of the Brothers In Arms franchise in a handheld gaming system. Players experience D-Day as a Screaming Eagle with more tactics and action exclusive to the PSP® system. Now players can surprise the enemy for the ultimate advantage in firefights, leading a fire team throughout the entire Normandy campaign. For the first time, players will also be able to lead a bazooka team, order their squad on an MG42, or fire mortar rounds. An enhanced co-op mode (Skirmish) offers players a 12-mission campaign. Co-op multiplayer (Skirmish mode): Play with a friend over ad hoc (wireless) through 12 different Skirmish missions in four different game modes through the co-op campaign.</desc>
    <releasedate>20061205T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Gearbox Software</developer>
    <publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Burnout Dominator (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (v1.01).iso</path>
    <name>Burnout Dominator</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Burnout Dominator is an installment of the Burnout series for the PlayStation 2 and the PlayStation Portable systems. The game is mainly focused on returned Burnouts feature - draining a complete boost meter without stopping wich was last seen in Burnout 2: Point of Impact. With return of Burnouts feature there were four new game modes added including Maniac Mode (players need to drive dangerously to get highest scores by earning drifts, air, oncoming and near misses. Chaining Burnouts in this mode increases the score multiplier), Drift Challenge (in this mode player need to obtain as many feet of drifting as possible. Chaining Burnouts also increases the score multiplier here), Near Miss Challenge (same as Drift Challenge, but player needs to score near miss bonuses), Burnout Challenge (also same as Drift Challenge, but focusing on obtaining Burnouts score). However, some options have been removed from the game - for instance Burnout Dominator doesn&apos;t feature Crash Mode, there is also no Traffic Checking Mode and Online Multiplayer. But PSP version features Burnout HQ where you can upload you score and download new track. The game consists of 12 different tracks, in 8 different real world locations. Each track has a forward and a reverse configuration.</desc>
    <releasedate>20070306T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Racing</genre>
    <players>4</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Call of Duty - Roads to Victory (Europe) (En,Fr,Es,It) (v1.02).iso</path>
    <name>Call of Duty - Roads to Victory</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Features &amp; details
Immersive Gameplay designed from the ground up, as an all-new Call of Duty experience
Players will face the full onslaught of the German war machine throughout 14 intense battles
Four precise control schemes, allowing players to select the one that ensures an optimal handheld experience
Players will be able to effortlessly change stance from standing to prone, throw grenades and target enemies in order to survive this ultimate WWII combat experience
Multiplayer options for up to 2-6 players to pick-up-and-go in modes such as Deathmatch, Capture the Flag and King of the Hill for quick hitting, over the top action</desc>
    <releasedate>20070313T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Amaze Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Activision</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Dante&apos;s Inferno (Europe).iso</path>
    <name>Dante&apos;s Inferno</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Dante&apos;s Inferno will take gamers to the western world&apos;s most definitive view of the afterlife as created by the 13th century Italian poet Dante Alighieri. Each of the nine circles will showcase its own distinct look, with demons, monsters and geography that are crafted straight from the poem&apos;s vivid descriptions. Using Death&apos;s Scythe and Beatrice&apos;s Holy Cross, and a slate of magic powers with a deep, customizable upgrade system, players will experience a fast and fluid 60 frames-per-second gameplay experience.</desc>
    <releasedate>20100301T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>EA Redwood Shores</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Daxter (Europe).iso</path>
    <name>Daxter</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Daxter is centered around the world of the lovable orange ottsel made popular in the Jak and Daxter franchise. The story unfolds as Daxter searches for Jak, who was imprisoned during the events that led to the start of &quot;Jak II.&quot; Daxter, now on his own in an unfamiliar place, quickly realizes that being small and furry won&apos;t help his chances of survival. To help stamp out a mysterious metalbug infestation, Daxter takes on a job as a pest exterminator, enabling him to explore parts of Haven City in an effort to collect the clues that will lead him to Jak. Daxter allows gamers to play from his perspective offering a distinctive set of moves with agile abilities that allows players to climb walls, creep up on enemies, fit in small places and maneuver vehicles. Taking a job as a pest exterminator, to fight an ongoing invasion of metal-bugs, Daxter comes equip with gadgets to rid the city of these metal nuisances. Get close up and personal by using your flimsy bug swatter to squash an army of attacking insects or your spray gun to hover around a variety of environments while picking up various upgrades.</desc>
    <releasedate>20060314T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Ready at Dawn</developer>
    <publisher>Sony</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Platform</genre>
    <players>24</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Def Jam - Fight for NY - The Takeover (Europe).iso</path>
    <name>Def Jam - Fight for NY - The Takeover</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Def Jam Fight for NY takes the battle for hip-hop domination into the fighting ring. More than 35 hip-hop artists and personalities--including Busta Rhymes, Carmen Electra, Lil&apos; Kim, Ludacris, Method Man, Redman, Sean Paul, Slick Rick, and Snoop Dogg--face off in brutal wrestling matches. In the ring and on the streets, you&apos;ll join the battle as a New York City street fighter. The game challenges you to develop your own fighting style and seize control of the hip-hop underworld.</desc>
    <releasedate>20060829T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>AKI Corporation</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Fighting</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/God of War - Chains of Olympus (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).iso</path>
    <name>God of War - Chains of Olympus</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The game is set in Ancient Greece and loosely based on its mythology. The player controls Kratos, a Spartan warrior in the service of the Olympian Gods. Kratos is guided by the goddess Athena, who instructs him to find the Sun God Helios, as the Dream God Morpheus has caused the remaining gods to slumber in Helios&apos; absence. With the power of the sun, Morpheus and Persephone, the Queen of the Underworld, with the aid of the Titan Atlas, intend to destroy the Pillar of the World and in turn Olympus. God of War: Chains of Olympus is chronologically the second chapter in the series, which focuses on vengeance as its central theme.</desc>
    <releasedate>20080304T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Ready at Dawn</developer>
    <publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/God of War - Ghost of Sparta (Europe).iso</path>
    <name>God of War - Ghost of Sparta</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Set in the realm of Greek mythology, God of War: Ghost of Sparta is a single-player game that allows players to take on the powerful role of Spartan warrior Kratos. This new adventure picks up after God of War concludes, telling the story of Kratos&apos; ascension to power as the God of War. In his quest to rid himself of the nightmares that haunt him, Kratos must embark on a journey that will reveal the origins of lost worlds, and finally answer long-awaited questions about his dark past. Armed with the deadly chained Blades of Chaos, he will have to overcome armies of mythological monsters, legions of undead soldiers, and amazingly dangerous and brutal landscapes throughout his merciless quest.</desc>
    <releasedate>20101102T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Ready at Dawn</developer>
    <publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Gran Turismo (Europe).iso</path>
    <name>Gran Turismo</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>The game is centered on an open-ended design. The single-player menu presents players with three variables — Mode Selection (Time Trial, Single Race, and Drift Trial), Car Selection, and Track Selection. The player can pick and choose circuits and vehicles, with credits earned based on the difficulty, performance and number of laps they have chosen. Players can select from any number of laps, one to 99. There are 45 tracks (including layout variations) plus the added bonus of reverse on most tracks, which takes the track number close to 75. For the first time in the series, the game features the use of custom soundtracks that enables players to play their own songs while racing, but this option must first be unlocked by completing section B of the Driving Challenges. The music tracks can only be played if it is set on &quot;MUSIC folder&quot; and can be used for offline or online races.</desc>
    <releasedate>20091001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Polyphony Digital Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Sony</publisher>
    <genre>Racing</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Killzone - Liberation (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Pl,Ru).iso</path>
    <name>Killzone - Liberation</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>In Killzone: Liberation, two months after the events of &quot;Killzone,&quot; (PS2) most of southern Vekta is still under Helghast control. The rules of war have been cast aside with the Helghast General, Metrac, employing brutal measures in order to seize the initiative and strengthen his position further. Returning as Templar, players will be sent on a mission to undertake a covert operation to save hostages captured by Metrac, while ISA troops continue the fight for liberty. Featuring an intelligent third person camera system, Killzone: Liberation allows players a more tactical surveillance viewpoint to view their action and read the enemy&apos;s behavior during gameplay. Set in an intense postmodern war reminiscent of the previous PS2 title, Killzone: Liberation features the unique graphical style to showcase pure grit and realism. During gameplay, players will have access to variety of weapons that are unique and innovative, inspired by modern military equipment.</desc>
    <releasedate>20061031T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Guerrilla Games</developer>
    <publisher>SCEA</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
    <players>4</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Metal Slug XX (USA).iso</path>
    <name>Metal Slug XX</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Metal Slug XX is an entry in the long-running series of side-scrolling shooters. It is a revised version of Metal Slug 7. The Peregrine Falcons, Marco, Eri, Clark, Tarma, Fio and Ralf, are once again running-and-gunning in colorfully hand-drawn levels, throwing grenades, driving vehicles and slashing enemies.

Metal Slug XX includes various single-player features in the form of a Combat School that lets players return to previously completed missions while executing various objectives; a POW List that shows how many POWs were rescued in each level; and single-player Rankings. Players can also cooperate in Ad-Hoc while gunning down hordes of humorous foes using familiar weapons in seven distinct levels that will see our heroes traverse deserts, mountains, caves and lava pits to finally put an end to their longtime enemy.

This revised version includes additional content including co-op multiplayer and downloadable content, as well as the character Leona Heidern.</desc>
    <releasedate>20100223T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SNK Playmore</developer>
    <publisher>Atlus U.S.A., Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Need for Speed - Most Wanted (Europe).iso</path>
    <name>Need for Speed - Most Wanted</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Need for Speed: Most Wanted (commonly abbreviated to as NFS: MW or just Most Wanted) is a racing video game developed by EA Black Box and published by Electronic Arts. It is the ninth installment in the Need for Speed series. The game features street racing-oriented game play, with certain customization options from the Need for Speed: Underground series. The game is succeeded by Need for Speed: Carbon, which serves as a sequel to Most Wanted.

Most Wanted has been released for Nintendo DS, Microsoft Windows, PlayStation 2, Xbox, GameCube, Game Boy Advance and is the first Need for Speed game released for the seventh generation console, the Xbox 360, as one of the system&apos;s launch titles. Another version of Most Wanted, titled Need for Speed: Most Wanted 5-1-0 has been released for the PlayStation Portable. In May 2012, the PlayStation 2 version was released on the online virtual market, PlayStation Store, for the PlayStation 3. On June 1, 2012, a reboot of the game, also called Need for Speed: Most Wanted, was announced by the British developing team Criterion Games and was released on October 30, 2012.

Need for Speed: Most Wanted received positive reviews and was a commercial success; it sold 16 million copies worldwide, making it the best-selling title in the series</desc>
    <releasedate>20051115T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>EA Canada</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Racing, Vehicle Simulation</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Prince of Persia - Rival Swords (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (v1.06).iso</path>
    <name>Prince of Persia - Rival Swords</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>In Prince of Persia Rival Swords, the Prince makes his way home to Babylon, bearing with him Kaileena, the enigmatic Empress of Time, and unspeakable scars from the Island of Time. But instead of the peace he longs for, he finds his kingdom ravaged by war and Kaileena the target of a brutal plot. When she is kidnapped, the Prince tracks her to the palace – only to see her murdered by a powerful enemy. Her death unleashes the Sands of Time, which strike the Prince and threaten to destroy everything he holds dear. Cast out on the streets, hunted as a fugitive, the Prince soon discovers that the Sands have tainted him, too. They have given rise to a deadly Dark Prince, whose spirit gradually possesses him.</desc>
    <releasedate>20070403T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Pipeworks Software, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
    <genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Pro Evolution Soccer 2014 (Europe).iso</path>
    <name>Pro Evolution Soccer 2014</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Pro Evolution Soccer 2014 centers everything on the ball including how it moves and how players use it. First touch and sublime control are what set certain players apart from others. The ability to not only read a pass, but to be one step ahead and to know what is needed to gain yards on an encroaching defender. Trueball Tech allows the player to trap or knock on a pass using the analogue stick with detailed bar-centric physics determining the weight shift of the player and the height and speed of the pass, as to how the player&apos;s body will automatically shape to receive it. The Pro Evolution Soccer series has long since treated the ball as an individual entity, allowing the player huge amounts of freedom to pass into space, run on to a knocked-on counter, or produces short triangular passes to make space. Trueball Tech adds even more freedom, with full 360-degree control within several yards around the player and the ability to shield the ball from opposing players, use deft controls to wrong-foot them, and intuitive methods to master close control.</desc>
    <releasedate>20131114T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>2</players>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Pro Evolution Soccer 6 (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It) (v1.03).iso</path>
    <name>Pro Evolution Soccer 6</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc>Winning Eleven: Pro Evolution Soccer 2007 expands upon the series&apos; realism with faster gameplay, more responsive control and improved artificial intelligence. Players will now make intelligent runs without the ball, identifying opportunities and pointing to where they would like the ball to be delivered. Similarly, the game is now more physical, with defenders jockeying for position and strikers working to turn their opponent as they receive the ball. The game&apos;s shooting system has also been refined, letting players take more snap shots, while volleys have been updated for more player control.

Players can also enjoy the Beautiful Game in more ways than ever before with new play modes. International Challenge mode lets players compete through four continents of opposition to become a champion, while Random Selection Match lets gamers take the field with a group of players selected at random from a predetermined league or geographic area. The Master League mode returns with more options, allowing players to take complete control of their favorite team and control its destiny for an extended period of time. The game&apos;s roster of teams is also expanded with new, fully-licensed international teams for players to use including Argentina, Italy, the Netherlands, Spain and Sweden, as well as additional club teams.</desc>
    <releasedate>20070206T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players />
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>/home/gabriel/RetroPie/roms/psp/Warriors, The (Europe) (v1.02).iso</path>
    <name>The Warriors</name>
    <thumbnail />
    <image />
    <marquee />
    <video />
    <rating />
    <desc />
    <releasedate />
    <developer />
    <publisher />
    <genre />
    <players />
  </game>
</gameList>